[Subtitles by that bilge rat danielsangeo]
Arr, these caverns be no place for
a gentleman of fortune such as meself.
I sees no more agitators in the forward,
I best be plottin' a new
course for the topside.
Me mechanical longboat
been servin' me true.
I hope the musket fire changed
your inclination none.
What be here?
Arr, down's not the way I be seekin'.
I already done spend enough time
below deck to last me two lives over.
Well, enough hemmin' and hawin',
it be high time I aweighed
anchor and shoved off.
'Tis true of the--what be that noise?
Arr, these caves be haunted, says I.
But, livin' and dead alike shall bow
before the great Cap'n Freeman.
Avast!
Gunner off the starboard bow!
Arr har har har!
I deadlights captured thee afore
ye could repel boarders.
Didn't care for the taste of me
repeatin' flintlock, did ye now?
Well, blow me down for an old sea calf.
'tis a beauty of a cannon, that there is.
I'll be mountin' that on me vessel once
I's done explorin' this fort's armory.
Arr, I could surely go for a
bottle of rum right now.
Ahoy there!
HECU: Movement!
You lunkheaded milksops!
Don't you know who you're
quarrelin' with?!
I be the great pirate Freeman!
[machine gun fire]
Arr, that way be soundin'
a mite dangerous-like.
Perchance I be goin' this way.
Sink me.
Well, ain't you the sly one?
Gettin' the drop on ol' Freeman.
'Tis of no matter; I'll lays all athwart.
I sees there be no treaty to be
made what with the likes of thee.
If it's a fair fight you're lookin' for,
then you've come to the wrong man.
Yarr, the battle be ragin' outside,
making now the perfect time to plunder.
Devil burn me!  These stores be
filled with empty boxes!
What manner of trickery be behind this?
Arr, enough of these monkeyshines.
It's time I be handin' out a
lesson in humility to these swabs.
I'll load up me miniature
grapeshot for the task.
One blast of this and they'll be wishin'
they were in a different line of work.
Come back, you cowardly cur!
Arr, the bloodlettin' be flowin' over.
I shows no quarter to
lubbers such as thee.
You call yourselves Marines, but
mariners I says you're not.
I bet none of ye could
rig a bunt gasket
'round a master jigger if your lives
were hangin' in the balance.
Arr.
But I do thank ye for all the munitions
ye swabs been providin' me with.
It be a shame for them to go to waste
what with so many of
thee left to cut down.
Fire the cannon!
Arr har har har har har!
Them that dies be the lucky ones!
And there be plenty o'
luck goin' round today!
A-har-har-har-har....
By thunder, what be this?
I knows--
Arr, I knows not what be
transgressin' here,
but in my sight, you're all not
better than a bunch of fightin' cocks.
Now, what do we have here?
An anti-scurvy machine.
Shiver me timbers!
By the powers!  There be all manner
of queer beasties in this hold.
I cares not for 'em.
Now, what booty be so special
here if it weren't guarded, I asks.
I aims to find out.
Arr, this must be the brig.
GUARD: Hello.
You stinkin' bilge rat!
I swears, the men behind this
mess will all swing for sure.
Ho there, squire!
What say ye to joinin' me crew?
I gives you me affidavi', I'll give
you a cut of any loot we take.
GUARD: Okay, why not?
Yarr--
GUARD: Didn't want to die alone anyway.
Yarr!  That be the spirit!
Let us charge forth and paint
the walls red with blood!
GUARD: I don't know if we should
go any further.
GUARD: Th-this doesn't look right.
Quakin' in your booties, now are ye?
Ye yellow-bellied sapsucker!
Just follow me!
Arr, get down!
Get down, I says!
You blunderin' squid!
What good are ye now?
A fine mate you turned out to be!
Curse it all!
Arr...
That jack be right handy at his post.
Unlike some I could name.
Arr, I best be awaitin' this one out.
I wasn't goin' to give that
swab any of the loot anyhow.